{
  "whale": [
    {
      "animal": "Blue Whale",
      "question": "what do whales eat?",
      "answerOne": "Sea Kelp",
      "answerTwo": "Plankton",
      "answerThree": "Sharks",
      "correctAnswer": "answerTwo"
    },
    {
      "animal": "Blue Whale",
      "question": "How big is a Blue Whale?",
      "answerOne": "As big as a car",
      "answerTwo": "The same size as a Giraffe",
      "answerThree": "As big as two buses",
      "correctAnswer": "answerThree"
    },
    {
      "animal": "Blue Whale",
      "question": "what do whales eat?",
      "answerOne": "Sea Kelp",
      "answerTwo": "Plankton",
      "answerThree": "Sharks",
      "correctAnswer": "answerTwo"
    }
  ],
  "axolotl": [
    {
      "animal": "axolotl",
      "question": "where do they live?",
      "answerOne": "In rivers",
      "answerTwo": "Outside, in the forest",
      "answerThree": "In caves",
      "correctAnswer": "In caves"
    },
    {
      "animal": "axolotl",
      "question": "What colour are most pet Axolotls?",
      "answerOne": "Pink",
      "answerTwo": "Yellow",
      "answerThree": "Green",
      "correctAnswer": "Pink"
    },
    {
      "animal": "axolotl",
      "question": "what do Axolotls eat?",
      "answerOne": "Insects, worms and small fish",
      "answerTwo": "Plants, algae and eggs",
      "answerThree": "Small rocks, twigs and leaves",
      "correctAnswer": "Insects, worms and small fish"
    }
  ],
  "penguin": [
    {
      "animal": "Adele penguin",
      "question": "where do they live?",
      "answerOne": "The Antarctic, on the snow",
      "answerTwo": "African coast, on the beaches",
      "answerThree": "British coast, in the rain",
      "correctAnswer": "The Antarctic, on the snow"
    },
    {
      "animal": "Adele penguin",
      "question": "How deep can an Adele dive?",
      "answerOne": "The deep bit of a swimming pool",
      "answerTwo": "As deep as England's deepest lake, Wastwater",
      "answerThree": "As deep as 3 Olympic swimming pools end to end",
      "correctAnswer": "As deep as 3 Olympic swimming pools end to end"
    },
    {
      "animal": "Emperor Penguin",
      "question": "what do Emperor Penguins eat?",
      "answerOne": "Fish",
      "answerTwo": "Seals and Polar Bears",
      "answerThree": "Starfish and sea snails",
      "correctAnswer": "Fish"
    }
  ],
  "cat":[
    {
      "animal": "Snow Leopard",
      "question": "where do they live?",
      "answerOne": "The Antarctic, on the snow",
      "answerTwo": "African savannah",
      "answerThree": "Himalayan mountains",
      "correctAnswer": "Himalayan mountains"
    },
    {
      "animal": "Cheetah",
      "question": "What is a Cheetah best at?",
      "answerOne": "Running the fastest",
      "answerTwo": "Jumping the farthest",
      "answerThree": "Swimming the deepest",
      "correctAnswer": "Running the fastest"
    },
    {
      "animal": "(domesticated) pet cats",
      "question": "How long have people been keeping cats?",
      "answerOne": "Before the Ancient Egyptians",
      "answerTwo": "Since the Ancient Romans",
      "answerThree": "Since the Victorians",
      "correctAnswer": "Before the Ancient Egyptians"
    }
    ]
}